FILING FOR LOVE
EPISODE 4:
PLAYING WITH FIRE
FRIENDSHIP BEYOND PARTNERSHIP
James is an innovator
who greatly advanced AI technology.
It took great effort to invite him.
FUTURE OF HAEMU'S TECH INNOVATION
First of all, thank you so much for having me.
And I really apperciate all the support...
Thank you.
You know, I truly feel like Mr. Jeon...
Ms. Joo must be at work by now.
Let's avoid her as best I can today.
Mr. Noh, Good morning.
How come we meet right here?
It's a small company, isn't it?
It's your lucky day.
I'll treat you to a coffee.
- No, I don't want...
- What is it? An Americano? A latte?
Are you a die-hard
iced Americano fan?
I am.
What?
How can she be so nonchalant?
She must've seen me.
He enjoys the spotlight too much.
Act natural
like I always have.
That James guy.
He enjoys the spotlight too much.
I get that scouting him
is your greatest achievement yet...
Let's focus on the sport.
Go!
That was a close miss.
You almost got the last one.
I'm getting so old,
I can't even pull a trigger.
The shotgun is pretty hefty.
Shall we switch to a pistol?
Hitting a target is no fun.
There's no prey and it's still.
You're a true sniper at heart,
Father.
The day you first took me hunting.
That's when I decided.
That I would be a good, obedient boy
because my father's scary.
You cheeky monkey.
Why don't you two have a shoot-off?
It's been a while since I watched.
- It must've been like war.
- It was.
The staff got worried
they would shoot each other.
It looks like the time has come
to make up our minds
about which of the two
we should root for.
Don't you think our fate
depends on who Ms. Joo sides with?
I don't think
Ms. Joo will take sides.
She's straight as an arrow.
Mr. Ahn.
Yes, I'm coming, Ms. Joo.
How can I act like nothing happened?
It's just not the same.
What kind of art studio
has such flimsy security?
If they teach a class like that
shouldn't they at least
lock the doors?
You're saying Haemu Electronics'
Junior Engineer Lim Ha-kyong's case
will be investigated
separately by the research center?
Yes, it's a simple case
so the center's HR department
will investigate
and all we have to do
is review the report.
We'll take this case.
- I'll come with you.
- Okay.
No, wait, what?
You'll go and investigate yourself?
Yes, since the new CTO
James Lockett joined
they renovated the interior
to give it a Silicon Valley feel.
Let's take a day-trip
to get some air and look around.
But I have
a one-on-one meeting today.
Oh, do you?
In that case...
Who wants to go
to the research center with me?
Teams One and Two are
mostly at other subsidiaries
for the routine audit season,
so they have no manpower to spare.
Yes, you're right.
Then who wants to with me
from Team Three?
I've been under a lot of stress
due to a chain of events
and my bowels are acting up. Sorry.
Oh, no. I must dash.
Any volunteers?
Jeez, this is driving me crazy.
All right.
I might as well face her head-on.
- So...
- Isn't it a lovely day?
Yes, but Ms. Joo...
Shall we have some udon noodles
at the rest area later?
There was one place
with an awesome broth.
I think it was the rest area
with trampolines for kids.
- Ms. Joo, about yesterday...
- No! Don't talk.
I need to concentrate
when I'm driving.
I can't multitask
so I can't drive if you talk.
Let's go in silence.
- Still, I...
- I told you not to speak.
See? I almost missed the exit.
You do all the talking.
You charged 57,250 won
on the company card
and have four strikes
for poor attitude.
Read it slowly and carefully.
Okay.
CONFIRMATION OF AUDIT: LIM HA-KYONG
Who did you upset?
- Pardon?
- You were obviously targeted.
The personal charges
on your company card.
That happened too long ago
to penalize you now.
Being five to ten minutes late?
You don't report someone
to the head office
for poor work ethics
for going to a bank.
Who did you mess with
that a junior engineer
would become a target?
The Audit Team is
an independent department.
You can speak freely,
without any concerns.
Your secrets are safe with us.
Well, actually...
Hey, what's going on here?
Everybody, nice to meet you all. I'm James.
- Hi, James. Nice to meet you.
- Hey.
Nice to meet you.
I wanted to meet you, Ms. Joo.
Apologies, James,
but we're in the middle of the meeting.
I see that.
Oh my gosh, what did you do?
Ms. Joo, Ha-kyong...
Take it easy on her, okay?
Alright, so...
Let's get it done quickly.
And why don't we all have some coffee in my office?
Sounds good?
- Okay, sure.
- Yeah.
Alright. I'll see you there.
- Perfect. Let's go guys.
- Bye.
Let's sit.
Would you like to continue
what you were saying earlier?
What?
I have nothing else to say.
I'll just admit
to all the wrongdoings.
Your coffees are here.
- Oh, great.
- Thanks so much.
- A hot Americano, right?
- Yes, thanks.
- Thank you.
- Have a snack.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
I shall try this one.
- That tastes really good.
- It's the famous...
- Mr. Sung?
- Yes?
When will you give me
this quarter's expenditure list?
Hae-young.
Let us be. It's Children's Day.
- "Children's Day"?
- When the Head of Audit's away.
When the Head of Audit is away
- The world is ours for the taking
Since Ms. Joo's out,
I plan to take the afternoon off.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
You saw what Ms. Yoon did.
She took this afternoon off
then canceled it.
You shouldn't use paid time off
when your boss is away.
That's the truth.
I see there's so much more
for me to learn.
- When do you need that by?
- Hello, everyone. Please excuse me.
What brings you here,
Managing Director, sir?
Oh, well...
I should meet and greet
our Audit Team.
You're pretty powerful people.
Where's the star, Ms. Joo In-a?
She's out of the office on business.
It shouldn't take long.
- She should be back today.
- Is that so?
How about a team dinner
when Ms. Joo returns?
It's gizzard shad season.
Let's have some raw fish and soju.
It's my treat!
- Mr. Jeon!
Okay. Text me
when you've made the reservation.
- Yes, sir! Thank you!
- Thank you!
- Bye. We love you!
- Work hard!
- Yes, sir!
I should've taken the afternoon off.
This must be the first team dinner
since he came back.
Ms. Joo doesn't need to pick sides.
Her side came looking for her.
- Good for her.
- I should report to Ms. Joo.
- He's so tall.
- I'm excited.
Ms. Lim.
I got the impression
you didn't tell us the full story.
If you feel uneasy talking at work
do you want to talk elsewhere?
There's a phrase
the Audit Team quotes often.
"Police, prosecutor,
judge, and attorney."
We investigate like the police,
prosecute like a prosecutor
make a ruling like a judge
and defend the whistleblower
like an attorney.
If you wish to report something to us
from that moment on
we will act as your attorneys.
So...
You can trust us.
But you're still Haemu employees.
I was told the same last time.
That I should trust you and tell all.
What?
Ms. Lim.
- Hello, Mr. Moo.
- Is Ms. Joo there with you?
She's not answering her phone.
I'm not with her right now.
I'll get back to you.
Okay, bye.
Mr. Noh!
Get over here.
There are lots of interesting things.
James!
There you go!
How did you make something like this?
James, are you an alien?
Secret.
We suspect him, too.
His mind works
on a whole other level.
Right. He mastered Korean in no time.
He's a genius.
Don't you flatter me like that.
- James, your Korean is great!
- I know.
Oh, In Ah.
Do you play golf?
Of course.
Okay, because over here...
Sudden team dinner
with Managing Director Jeon.
Inform Ms. Joo for me.
A 100,000-won bet.
- How's that?
- Ms. Joo.
James, don't forget.
I'm from the audit department.
No money. But...
how about the loser gets a forehead flick?
I know that.
- Okay, deal.
- Deal.
Mr. Lee Seung-hyun is on
a New York business trip to prepare
for the unpacking later this year.
PR Team's Managing Director
Cheon Joo-won
is increasing contact
with the media to influence
how they report
our management issues.
We're keeping an eye on Choi Woo-tae
Haemu Chemicals' Vice CEO
who was rumored
to have received
a job offer from overseas.
How are things
between Directors Ma and Han?
They seemed to be fighting over
which accounting firm to hire.
They seem to have
reached an agreement.
The Planning Team
will report to you soon.
Managing Director Jeon seems
to have stepped in as a mediator.
Sung-yeol?
Yes, he has been meeting
the main executives in turn.
He's working hard.
This evening
he's joining the Audit Team dinner.
The Audit Team?
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Ms. Park.
What brings you to this lowly place?
Hello.
The vice president will attend
your team dinner as well.
- What?
- He can't eat raw food
so you should book a barbecue place.
Pick one with a decent wine stock.
Email me when you've found a place.
Bye, then.
- Okay.
Goodbye.
Why are we
suddenly at the center of attention?
Managing Director Jeon... Oh, right.
We booked a raw fish place.
The managing director
wanted gizzard shad.
- This is a disaster.
- No, wait.
Team Three is in charge
of the booking.
They should decide.
Okay, everyone.
Is it that serious an issue?
The managing director said
he wanted gizzard shad
and the vice president
can't eat raw fish.
What someone can't eat
takes precedent over want.
Don't you agree?
I'll book a barbecue restaurant.
Sorry.
It's not that simple an issue.
Hae-young, don't you see
how serious this matter is?
The Audit Team's fate
depends on this decision.
You can't be so rash.
The managing director was first.
Shall we have fish?
His was the prior engagement.
That's a decent excuse.
But the vice president
is higher in rank.
That might be viewed as insolence.
It's the biggest crisis of my career.
Oh, dear...
Nice.
Bravo!
What do you think you're doing?
There's definitely more
to this incident.
You suspected she was targeted, too.
We need to look into it.
We can't waste time playing golf.
Here we go.
Oh, nice shot!
Don't you see
how hard I'm working right now?
Nice, James.
Right. Nice, James.
- Are you next?
- Yes.
Good luck. Let's go, In Ah.
- Hello, Mr. Moo.
- Didn't you get my text?
Whether we should have
barbecue or raw fish.
Get her to decide for us.
What's keeping Ms. Joo so busy?
She's currently taking part
in a global competition.
What? She's doing a global what?
Okay, fine. Bye.
Oh, dear.
Hasn't he asked her yet?
We really need to make a booking now.
This is so stressful.
What should we do?
Look.
My hair's falling out from stress.
What should I do now?
Let's just eat both.
Meat and raw fish.
Are you suggesting a buffet?
I looked them up,
and none of them serve both.
You're wrong.
The galbi place we had
last year's year-end party at.
It's a barbecue restaurant,
but they also sell gizzard shad
that the owner's mother-in-law
sends from Namhae.
It's their seasonal offer.
Hey, you're right.
- Let me see.
- We found a place.
Let me take a look.
Why you... Take a look, sir.
My word.
Why are you sharing this now, Da-yae?
You should've told us
before I started to lose hair.
Hey, it was a great time.
I actually had a lot of fun today.
I had a great time, too, James.
And also...
I must say...
I'm rather impressed today.
I really think you're a great leader.
That's actually very flattering to hear.
Thank you.
You have nearly 10,000 employees.
And yet,
you personally know
how to care for junior staff
like Lim Ha-kyung.
Yeah, I mean...
What can I say...
It's because I love my people.
Give me a second.
Ms. Joo, your driver for hire
will take you back to Seoul.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
- Shall we?
- In-a, visit again.
Come here. I'm going to miss you.
Of course, James.
Take care, okay?
See you soon.
I'll see you.
Alright.
- Bye.
- Goodbye, James.
Hurry and get in the car.
Move it. Hurry.
Sir. Follow the car up ahead.
I'll pay you
double the fare to Seoul.
- Okay.
- Wear your seat belt.
I knew it.
We're following James, aren't we?
Will you tell me now
what we did all day long?
You didn't do all that
to befriend him, did you?
Earlier at the research center.
I looked up
James' company card statement.
The company
got him a room at the Baron Hotel
but he's been frequenting
the Rosa Hotel.
So what?
Do you suspect James?
I suspected him from the start.
The target
was a young female researcher.
But James is...
You know,
even if he's involved somehow
the higher-ups
will try to cover it up.
If this backfires
due to a careless move
you could be in serious trouble.
Exactly.
I'll make sure it doesn't backfire.
Here.
- Your check-in is complete.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Mr. Noh.
- Run.
- What?
We need his room number.
Get to it.
Hang on.
He got into the elevator.
What floor are you on?
The fifth floor.
Still?
Run faster.
Excuse me?
Jeez.
Nine, ten.
It's 13.
He got off at the 13th floor.
I saw him enter Room 1307.
Babe.
Come here. Hurry.
Yes, over here.
Look at you sweating.
Did you run so we could meet sooner?
Oh, yes, right, sweetie.
It's so hot.
You make a lovely couple.
Which room would you like?
We have rooms
with a city view, a park view...
Room 1306, please.
- Pardon?
- The thing is...
We're celebrating a special day.
We want to reminisce
on what we did in Room 1306 before.
Give me a moment.
- Okay.
- So that's it.
Oh, dear. I'm terribly sorry.
Someone already checked into 1306
and the room next door, 1307
just became unavailable.
What about Room 1308?
Oh, that room is available, but...
Since you're celebrating
a special day
how about we offer you
a free upgrade?
We're very proud of our suite...
No, we'll take Room 1308.
Our suite offers a much better view
- that I'm sure...
- We want to be...
as close to the special room
as possible.
Give us that room.
It means more to us than a room.
It's such a special memory.
Okay. Oh, gosh...
I'll help you check in
as soon as possible.
It's this way.
You put on a great show earlier.
Why are you hesitating now?
You've already seen everything.
Darn it.
MOTHER-IN-LAW'S
SEASONAL GIZZARD SHAD FROM NAMHAE
Shouldn't we seat the stepbrothers
across from each other?
That will make this the top seat
and that would be weird.
How about this layout?
We separate the two tables
so one has raw fish
and the other has barbecue.
Wouldn't it be too obvious
that we separated them?
- Right?
- Yes.
This is a headache...
You're here already.
Hello and welcome, sir.
Where should we seat you?
Sit wherever you want, sir.
What a bright idea
from our Gen Z employee.
Okay. I'll sit here, then.
Why not in the middle?
No, this is fine.
I can see all of you from here.
You can rotate after a while.
Okay. We'll do that.
The VP is here.
- Hello, sir.
What took you so long? I'm starving.
- You can all sit down.
- Sure.
Take a seat, everyone.
Did I make you wait long?
Gosh, no, sir.
We just placed the order,
and they'll start serving.
This is their wine list.
If there's anything you like...
Jae-yeol.
Don't drink wine. Soju is the drink
of choice for a team dinner.
Aren't I right?
Sure, soju sounds good.
- Right?
- Yes.
You can order whatever you like.
Okay.
I don't see Ms. Joo.
Is she not back yet?
Oh, I'll call and ask.
- Call Mr. Noh.
- Okay.
She's out on business
with Mr. Noh Ki-jun.
It's so hot.
Why are you undressing?
I'm drenched in sweat
because you made me run the stairs
to get the room number.
So hot.
- Hi, White Blood Cell.
- Mr. Noh.
Are you with Ms. Joo?
Yes, just a moment.
It's Mr. Baek.
- Yes, Mr. Baek?
- Ms. Joo.
Where about are you?
I'm in a hotel room.
We're here for dinner
with the VP and MD.
When can you get here?
- I'm staying the night.
- What?
- Pardon?
- Mr. Noh and I can't make it.
- Send my regards to the bosses.
- Ms. Joo, it's...
She hung up.
What did she say?
Well...
Ms. Joo and Mr. Noh are in a hotel.
They'll stay the night there.
- Both of them?
- Yes.
Ms. Joo, won't they get
the wrong idea if you say that?
I couldn't say
we were spying on James.
I only stated a fact.
Yes, but still...
Wait, I hear something.
What's wrong?
He's taking a shower.
What?
Okay, the rooms aren't soundproof.
You can sit over here, Mr. Noh.
Scoot over.
You can't sit on a cold floor.
Here you go.
I'm so thirsty.
This is a nice brand.
I'll drink this
instead of getting paid extra.
Are you really going to drink
in a hotel room?
Yes, because I'm so thirsty,
all thanks to someone.
What's wrong?
You said I've already seen it all.
- That was delicious.
- It was so good. I'm full.
Thank you for dinner, sir!
- Thank you!
- Thank you, sir!
- Hey, Min-su!
- Yes, sir!
Let's play pool sometime soon.
- Yes, and I won't let you win, sir.
- Please don't.
Sir, you have to follow me back
on Instagram.
Sure. No, while we're at it,
let me do it now.
Really? Awesome!
Sir, can you follow me, too?
Wait a second.
This is the kind of moment
I really love.
You're even funny!
Follow me!
Why don't we take a picture?
- Get inside.
- Jump in!
I'll take it now. One, two, three.
- Mr. Choi.
- Yes?
Let's stop by the pharmacy
for some headache pills.
All right.
I'll go and pick it up.
What an immature day.
Do I make you feel uncomfortable
because of my feelings for you?
Look at this right here.
Park A-jeong.
Your name is on the loan
as a guarantor.
And there's your seal.
I've never even seen this.
This is a crime!
Your older brother
is the one who conned us!
The lease here and everything else
don't amount to half of what he owes!
I gave him a good deal
because you had a good corporate job.
Why don't you use this chance
to take on a new job?
A pretty girl like you
only needs a month
to pay back everything you owe.
Mr. Vice President.
Hello.
My name is Park A-jeong
the new executive assistant
from last week.
I didn't expect you
to be at work this early.
To be exact, I never went home.
Why are you here already?
I got this place
to occasionally spend time alone
but I haven't had enough free time
to come here recently.
Feel free to stick around
for as long as you want.
I have most things you'll need.
But there's no food or water.
Do you want a drink?
Have a seat.
Let's skip this nonsense
and cut to the chase.
Do you want to shower first?
Or should I wash up first?
What's wrong?
Are you into something specific?
Just accept someone's kindness
as kindness itself.
If you think it's too much
think of it as an employee benefit.
Yes, the product is innovative.
However, it's hard for me
to see the roadmap
in the mid to long-term perspective.
To include this in Haemu's portfolio
not only do we need a good idea
but we need to see
a specific execution plan.
Yes.
Yes, I'll check the vice president's
schedule and get back to you.
Sure.
I got a bit drunk.
I have a question.
What are you
so tormented by?
You never eat but only drink alcohol
never sleep, and only work.
If I were as rich as you
I would only eat good food
and go out all the time.
I know that was a mistake.
It's late. You should go.
It wasn't a mistake.
I like you.
Mr. Jeon.
And it's not because I'm drunk.
And no, it's not
because of what you have.
I don't expect anything in return.
I understand your situation
and I already know my place.
I just
wanted to share
how I felt.
I'll pretend like I never heard it.
What happened in the art class
is more embarrassing for me.
"Should I go and kill myself?"
"No, should I kill Mr. Noh instead?"
I went back and forth
millions of times.
I knew it.
- You were just acting chill.
- Yes.
Jeez.
I'm sorry, anyway.
You must feel like you were violated.
After all, I was the intruder.
You had no idea when you came
to the art class, anyway.
Sorry?
Yes, right.
The recreational art class.
Tell me about it.
What are the chances?
Let me make this clear
in case you thought I had two jobs.
I don't get paid to do that.
It's like a hobby.
Yes, sure.
Something like a different job
didn't even cross my mind.
I couldn't think in that situation.
Anyway
may I ask you this?
Why did you take up that hobby?
That way, I can breathe.
I mean, you know.
Every office worker
needs something like that.
A place to breathe.
That's why.
But wait.
How are your feet so tiny?
What? My feet?
No, yours are just huge.
I don't think so.
Could you stop staring at my body?
What?
Goodness, how can you say that?
I also suffered
from a great psychological shock!
Are you saying my body was shocking?
Yes, of course!
No, wait.
I don't mean that in a bad way.
What I want to tell you is that
- it was shocking in a good way...
- So you liked it?
I mean, if I say I liked it
it can lead
to another misunderstanding.
What I want to say is this.
What I meant was...
So, now what? What do you want?
Should I just strip naked right now?
That will be fair.
- That's a great idea.
- What?
Are you serious right now?
Gosh, I can't deal with this.
Watch out!
Sorry?
Ha-kyung.
Come on in.
Have a seat.
Come on.
Sit down.
The Audit Team
from the head office is here.
Because of you.
Why are you causing trouble
for everyone?
What did you talk to those people about?
You didn't dare mention my name, right?
Okay, good. That's my girl.
Okay, good.
Hey, Ha Kyung, don't cry.
You're breaking my heart.
Don't be so uptight.
No need to make a big deal out of it.
You little piece of...
We're not done.
You stay here. Don't say a word. Okay?
Who is it?
- In Ah.
- Hi, James.
What are you guys doing here?
Are you out of your mind?
Remember our forehead smack bet?
I won that bet.
I wouldn't call that a smack.
That was a punch.
He asked for a meeting.
He had something to ask
about the research data.
I was concerned
that it was held at a hotel.
But that's where he had been staying
and I heard
he often held meetings there.
It was my mistake.
You didn't make a mistake, Ms. Lim.
Please don't blame yourself.
What are you going to do?
We were really ordered to do this.
We're unfairly blamed!
It's James, Ms. Joo. James...
- Thank you.
- You don't have to thank me.
The Audit Team did what it had to do.
She must be exhausted.
QUICK CONTROL
I have a question.
During Mr. Son's infidelity case
both Mr. Son
and Ms. Jeong were at fault
but you only let Mr. Son stay
in the head office.
- Yes.
- You said he was crucial to us.
You said morals were different
in the office
and we only had to care
about how it affects our company.
But James is way more crucial
than Mr. Son.
Why did you take things this far?
Isn't it obvious?
That was a crime.
He's expecting you.
You can wait here, Mr. Noh.
I'll report to him.
You two must've grown close.
I mean, you're standing here
like a puppy protecting its owner.
You used to say
a lot of bad things about her.
Are you picking a fight?
I don't appreciate
you staying the night out
without notice.
Hey, I didn't stay the night out.
And that's my home.
Hey, you're late.
Do you want a drink?
What's wrong with the vice president?
He looked like a pretty chill guy.
I've never seen him
like that, either.
- It's James we're talking about.
- But still.
He sexually assaulted
his junior staff member
and even conducted a targeted audit
when she reported him.
Who cares if he's James or Zeus?
We have to kick him out!
Why are you so invested in this?
You've never been interested
in justice.
I'm not talking about justice.
We're talking
about common sense, okay?
Now that
we're talking about common sense...
Last night,
what did you and Joo-In-a do
all alone in that room
throughout the night?
What? What about it?
I mean, it's common sense.
A man and a woman
spent a night in a hotel room.
Isn't that weird?
Hey, we were there to work.
Can't you see?
We caught a big fish like him.
I'm sure you two worked.
But did you spend
the entire time just working?
So nothing happened?
- Something happened.
- Nothing happened.
I was stunned for a second
because your argument was so absurd.
What's wrong with you?
Wash up and go to sleep.
Ms. Joo, the final report on James.
Now, this one.
Look at the scope of audit.
Yes.
Take a look at it.
It looks good on you.
Thank you for that.
REPORTING MS. JOO IN-A
SHE IS INVOLVED IN AN INAPPROPRIATE
WORKPLACE RELATIONSHIP
I ATTACH THE EVIDENCE
Mr. Noh.
Are you not coming
to the class today?
We're not doing quick sketches today.
And I forgot to make myself clear.
I don't mind having you there.
Those classes happen
only from time to time
and I can stop being the model.
It's all right.
It's fine by me, too.
Feel free to show up comfortably.
I don't feel comfortable.
And I have no reason to be there.
Hey.
You're not allowed to drink here.
Don't be a nightmare.
This is alcohol-free.
Anyway, why are you here?
No particular reason.
I had no one to talk to.
Don't you have any friends?
Poor guy.
Do you want to drink with me?
Don't say something like that.
Don't trust random guys out there
and drink with them
like it's nothing.
You need to be wary of them
and be cautious in this foreign land.
Why are you taking this out on me?
- What?
- Is your life in turmoil?
What's with you?
Have you still not found
the pretty girl's man?
I don't know who he is yet
- but I've made progress.
- No way!
Congrats, man.
You said you had to find him
to keep doing your job smoothly.
Isn't that good news?
It is.
It's great for me.
So why are you so annoyed?
It's great news.
I wonder.
Why am I so annoyed?
It's so annoying.
Thank you for that.
Have I always been this pretty?
Right?
You are pretty.
FILING FOR LOVE
A kiss definitely makes it official.
I apologize.
I shouldn't have done that
as your superior.
- Like I was under a magic spell.
- Was she the only one who kissed?
Why does she decide everything
on her own?
Even after the kiss
I thought an apology
would settle everything.
I want to know
if there's something more between us.
Do you want to sleep with me?
Do you?
Can it really happen?
Can you really fall for someone
you've known for so long?
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim